// java
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of these cannot be used for a variable name in Java?",
    answer: "keyword",
    options: [
      "identifier & keyword",
      "identifier",
      "keyword",
      "none of the mentioned"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which environment variable is used to set the java path?",
    answer: "JAVA_HOME",
    options: [
      "MAVEN_Path",
      "JavaPATH",
      "JAVA",
      "JAVA_HOME"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following is not an OOPS concept in Java?",
    answer: "Compilation",
    options: [
      "Compilation",
      "Polymorphism",
      "Inheritance",
      "Encapsulation"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is not the use of “this” keyword in Java?",
    answer: "Passing itself to the method of the same class",
    options: [
      " Referring to the instance variable when a local variable has the same name",
      "Passing itself to the method of the same class",
      "Passing itself to another method",
      "Calling another constructor in constructor chaining"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following is a type of polymorphism in Java Programming?",
    answer: "Compile time polymorphism",
    options: [
      "Multilevel polymorphism",
      "Multiple polymorphism",
      "Execution time polymorphism",
      "Compile time polymorphism"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is Truncation in Java?",
    answer: "Floating-point value assigned to an integer type",
    options: [
      "Floating-point value assigned to an integer type",
      "Floating-point value assigned to a Floating type",
      "Integer value assigned to floating type",
      "Integer value assigned to floating type"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: " Which exception is thrown when java is out of memory?",
    answer: "OutOfMemoryError",
    options: [
      "MemoryFullException",
      "MemoryOutOfBoundsException",
      "MemoryError",
      "OutOfMemoryError"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of these are selection statements in Java?",
    answer: "if()",
    options: [
      "if()",
      "for()",
      "break",
      "continue"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following is a superclass of every class in Java?",
    answer: "Object class",
    options: [
      "ArrayList",
      "Abstract class",
      "Object class",
      "String"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the below is not a Java Profiler?",
    answer: "JVM",
    options: [
      "JProfiler",
      "Eclipse Profiler",
      "JConsole",
      "JVM"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "_____ is used to find and fix bugs in the Java programs.",
    answer: "JDB",
    options: [
      "JVM",
      "JRE",
      "JDK",
      "JDB"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "An interface with no fields or methods is known as a ______.",
    answer:  "Marker Interface",
    options: [
      "Runnable Interface",
      "Marker Interface",
      "Abstract Interface",
      "CharSequence Interface"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "In which memory a String is stored, when we create a string using new operator?",
    answer: "Heap memory",
    options: [
      "Stack",
      "String memory",
      "Heap memory",
      "Random storage space"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "In java, jar stands for_____.",
    answer:  "None of the above",
    options: [
      "Java Archive Runner",
      "Java Application Resource",
      "Java Application Runner",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
  numb: 14,
  question: "If a thread goes to sleep",
  answer:  " It does not release any locks.",
  options: [
    "It releases all the locks it has.",
    "It does not release any locks.",
    "It releases half of its locks.",
    "It releases all of its lock except one."
  ]
}
];